So I'm crazy, but you're coming at me asking me if I'm transgender and if I'm gay and all of this stuff.
I told you multiple times I have a wife and a child.
There are plenty of homosexuals who are married women.
But you're calling me crazy while you're making crazy, illogical arguments.
Well, no, that's what you call a projection.
Why are you saying that?
He has his hair so I figured it would be a fucking transgender.
Why are you calling him?
I asked him. It was a question. It was a question.
I didn't say a nice person.
I'm a not nice person.
No, I'm a good person.
No problem. I'm not here for you. Don't worry.
Have you ever looked into the health effects of eating animals?
I'm very pro. I think the health effects of eating animals are amazing.
I think if this country needs to be more meat-based, it's what RFK Jr. brought.
You don't think we'd have more higher cholesterol, obesity, heart disease?
No, no, no. The problem is the problem is...
Are you asking people for permission before you invade here?
On a public school, it's my understanding I don't have to.
No, no, no. Now when you're talking to people...
It's fine. I don't mind. Yes.
That's when you're going into a conversation.
You can do it privately.
Can I film you, bro?
I mean, I would rather not, but also it's your right to do so and there's nothing I can do to stop you.
No, he's saying that you do have a right to say no.
No, no, no, no. I do not have a right to... I can say no, but he has no right to... He still can film me. I know the law.
There's a strong correlation between eating animals and all the top killers, cancer, heart disease, diabetes.
Right. So I think... I actually don't believe in that.
I think that it's sugar, excessive amounts of sugars and processed foods that are causing these things.
I think the going back to eating more animal products is healthy and that's the way we should be doing this.
So the cultures that eat animal products exclusively, the Eskimos, the Maasai, do you know what their average lifespan is?
So you're also referring... that's also a logical fallacy because you understand that there are lower health care standards in those societies you mentioned.
They live natural lives. They're in the wild. They eat animals.
That's not what I said.
Each animal is the healthiest food.
That's not what I said. That's not what I said.
I said that the cultures, the two cultures you mentioned have lower health care standards than we have.
So a lot of the meat-based cultures have some of the highest health spans... or I'm sorry, some of the highest GDP.
What does GDP have to do with anything?
What you're saying? You're saying that they don't have the ability to care for their...
I said that they have lower health care.
Iceland's a great example. Iceland eats a ton of meat and they have a high GDP and they have a really good health care system.
And therefore, sometimes they will show higher health spans because of their health care system.
Even though that they eat animals because they're putting their people on hospice and they're doing all this.
So bringing in an argument about money is not...
I didn't say about money.
You said health care, which is the more money we have, the more health care and drugs and medicine.
That is not true.
That's not true.
All of these things are...
There's the most money in health care spent in America and we do not have, as you guys know.
Yeah, because we're consuming stuff that kills death.
That's fine.
If we consume death, we beget death.
Wait a second.
Sorry, give me one second.
Sure.
I do want to talk to your friends who are pro-abortion.
Are you pro-abortion?
Are you pro-choice?
I'm pro-choice.